Introducing Pangolin — built for the Sola Security Hackathon
Sola's pipeline scans your GitHub workflows daily,
classifying findings and alerting your team
Our CLI pulls data from Sola MCP — the regex engine
scans 105 workflows in 0.1 seconds
Then GPT-5.5 goes deep — reasoning through
real attack chains
6 confirmed vulnerabilities, 0 false positives,
29 proof-of-concept files generated
The report shows severity breakdown, attack scenarios,
and downloadable PoC files
Detection isn't enough — one command generates
a fix and opens a GitHub PR
Full vulnerability context and clean diff
Everything flows to Slack — alerts, reports,
fix notifications. A complete security loop.
Pangolin. Scan. Analyze. Fix. Automatically.